in this sprint
在这个冲刺
I will start with first day
我将从第一天开始
I do not know why
我不知道为什么
i
我
because he comforted me
因为他安慰我
for the children's favor
为了孩子们的爱
in this name
用这个名字
in sprint
在冲刺中
expressed by your interest the permit
以您的利益表示许可
superman my book change
超人我的书换
water and sell
卖水
avn
AVN
i
我
del grau
德尔格劳
bye
再见
Y
和
d
d
muse sbif action amendment
缪斯自尽行为修正案
in
在
in this segment
在这个细分市场
exist
有
the mavericks will look for you
特立独行者会找你
have psoe fall
psoe跌倒了
james life
詹姆斯生活
ah
啊
come on
来吧
[Music]
[音乐]
but none
但没有
efe
fe
and then
然后
i
我
good
好吧
one
1个
I
我
ah
啊
and not
而且没有
in defending
在捍卫
and good
好吧
up to date
一天
to piqué
去皮克
that is because
那是因为
because I do not
为什么不是我
by definition back
根据定义返回
fear of the pin was discounted
担心别针被打折
no father loring singler
没有父亲将单身汉
we have
我们有
ah
啊
today
今天
Y
和
because someone scams you
因为有人骗了你
keep my
保持我的
says now that it heats up
说现在加热
California
加州
and they don't like to be true
他们不喜欢真实
the thyroid rolón would appreciate it
甲状腺rolón会很感激的
surprised this scenario from you
使您感到惊讶
ah
啊
in the 2nd because they are
在第二，因为他们是
Pressure
压力
dental foundation member of action try
牙科基金会行动成员
[Music]
[音乐]
in the market
在市场上
Y
和
yes
是的
in which those buildings grandmasters
那些建筑物的宗师
ah
啊
Y
和
s
s
water contained to unai yus uribe mango
乌奈乌斯乌比芒果芒果所含的水
mens
人
who follows the handle and shape
谁跟随手柄和形状
and after dialing
和拨号后
so
在某种程度上
Y
和
excess of english
英语过剩
so far another way
到目前为止，另一种方式
getty i
盖蒂我
no sprint division uruguay user
没有冲刺部乌拉圭用户
sheltered
庇护
move to the country
搬到乡下
in that copy to practice is good
在那个副本上练习好
what
什么
are very expensive
他们很贵
efe
fe
Mary Kate Applications
Mary Kate应用
master serviu version
主服务版本
[Music]
[音乐]
and good
好吧
can be
可以
willy nice
威利·尼斯
okay
好吧
say bari
说巴里
in six months
在六个月内
perfect
完美的
s
s
with way of life
与生活方式
or
或
super
超级
good
好
start
开始
they want to be better
他们想变得更好
Wilkinson study me
威尔金森研究我
hawking
叫卖
is
是
[Music]
[音乐]
in 55
在55
informed
知情的
who know 70 of the truth
谁知道真相的70
and water
和水
it didn't have to be
不一定是
but also
而且
finish
结束
you get
你得到
[Music]
[音乐]
I public signing
我公开签名
want to see
想看
on this front
在这方面
in context
在上下文中
efe
fe
perform the
执行它
hunger
饥饿
d
d
of end
结束
ah
啊
major handle
大把柄
higher
专业
why
为什么
I love you from my eyes
我从我的眼睛爱你
all audiences
所有观众
ah
啊
no
没有啦
from spain place
从西班牙的地方
Y
和
Amen
阿门
than
什么
yellow
黄色的
extension of times
时间的延长
and they lost
他们输了
mediafire alone
单独的媒体大火
this mess
这个烂摊子
spring bennett
春天贝内特
5 news
5条新闻
of fa
发的
Y
和
yam
名
good
好
working
工作中
ah
啊
than
什么
[Music]
[音乐]
good
好
in the remaining years for 531
在剩下的531年中
break off
分离
because if they are explained why it is
因为如果他们解释了为什么
if I had it
如果我有
resting and it's the big one
休息，这是最大的
ah
啊
before experts
在专家面前
during this time
在这个时候
ah
啊
Y
和
but federer is good
但是费德勒很好
in your report
在您的报告中
get into that
进入那个
so it is a faction network to iniesta
所以这是伊涅斯塔的派系网络
before
之前
respectively for 15-12
分别为15-12
you are welcome
不客气
in spain
在西班牙
it's possible
有可能
here
在这里
i
我
I used the roberts spinning website
我使用了罗伯茨纺纱网站
good
好吧
[Music]
[音乐]
then the tobacco integration
然后烟草整合
though
虽然
some are there
有一些
d
d
I'll play
我要去玩
to
到
springsteen
Springsteen
for what
为了什么
came
来了
and not
而且没有
now winter springs
现在是冬泉
ah
啊
eject
弹出
Y
和
after - likes from first phillips
后-喜欢第一个菲利普
good
好吧
no
没有啦
efe
fe
when the money
当钱
to sports
体育
good
好吧
I'm going to have a little
我要去一点
Let's see
看
my confirm swings
我确认摇摆
of water
水
in that fact
事实上
Y
和
yes
是的
than
什么
by shepherds
由牧羊人
Toad
蟾蜍
wholesalers check out is
批发商退房是
monthly defenses in the world without extra
每月无需额外的防御